

- +381 69 34 30 321
- ◀ Belgrade, Serbia, RS
- stevan.stanisic@outlook.com
- **%** evansit.dev
- Twitter
- in LinkedIn
- GitHub



# ABOUT

Skilled System Administrator with 3+ years of wide knowledge of Operating Systems & Terminal and Full Stack Developer who can build web and mobile apps from the ground up. I have experience working with clients as well as company work. Always committed to professional growth and improving skills.



# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Microsoft Cloud Services Administrator, ITACET

April 2017 — June 2019 **②** 2 years

ITACET is Microsoft's gold partner and cloud solution provider.

- Planning and implementing cloud onboarding solutions for new and potential clients
- Manage and administer over 2500 user accounts and devices hosted on AzureAD
- Provide technical support, responding to service requests and resolving issues
- Workflow and infrastructure deployment automation with PowerShell

# Freelance Software Developer, EVANSIT (ss@evansit.dev)

October 2018 — Present ② 2 years

My previous extensive knowledge of PowerShell (Object-Oriented) scripting language encouraged me to dive deeper into programming and helped my self-tough developer/entrepreneur growth.

- Started a Company



**PROJECTS** 

#### TermoNik, Website

December 2019 — December 2019 ② 10 days

Example client work, technologies used:

- Frontend: ReactJS / Gatsby, Material UI, GraphQL
- Backend: Contentful (Headless CMS)
- CDN: Netlify

# Korona SRB, Mobile App

May 2020 — Present **②** 6 months

Example side project, technologies used:

- Frontend: Dart / Flutter, RESTful API, Firebase
- Backend: GCP
- CI/CD: GitHub Actions



# **EDUCATION**

### Information Technology (incomplete), Bachelors

2013 — 2014 **②** 2 years

The University of Belgrade

# </> > SKILLS

Front-End — *Master* 

HTML5 / JSX CSS3 / Bootstrap / Styled Components JavaScript / TypeScript

ReactJS / Gatsby RESTful API / GraphQL / Firebase

Back-End — Master

Node.js Express.js .NET Framework ASP.NET NuGet WPF

Mobile — Master

Dart Flutter React Native

DataBases — Fluent

CRUD MS SQL Server MongoDB Serverless

Cloud & DevOps — Fluent

Git GitHub Actions GitLab GCP Azure Azure DevOps Azure Functions Doker CI/CD



MCSA: Office 365, Microsoft

Awarded on: Sep 01, 2017

Microsoft Certified Solution Associate

PowerShell: Certificate of Completion , Admin Training Center

Awarded on: Feb 13, 2019

Trainer: Aleksandar Nikolic, Microsoft MVP

LANGUAGES

English, Fluent